MANAS DUTTA

WEB DEVELOPER



CONTACT

+91-9382867219

manasdutta1509@gmail.com

https://manasdutta.my.canva.site/

Garhbeta, West Bengal, India, 721127

SKILLS

- C Programming Language
- Python Programming Language
- HTML
- CSS
- MS Powerpoint
- MS Excel
- GitHub
- Figma

EDUCATION

B. Tech in Computer Science Engineering

Techno Engineering College Banipur 2022 - Present

Currently pursuing B. Tech in CSE

Intermediate

Garhbeta High School (H.S.)

2020-2022

Passed 12th Exam || Grade: A+

Matriculation

Garhbeta High School (H.S.)

2018-2020

Passed 10th Exam || Grade: A+

LANGUAGES

Bengali	
English	
Hindi	

PROFILE

Hey there! I'm a 19-year-old computer science engineering enthusiast on a journey to explore the digital world one code at a time. Currently, I'm pursuing my B. Tech in Computer Science and Engineering from TECB, and I'm absolutely thrilled to share my passion for technology with you.

Coding is my forte, and I'm well-versed in languages like C and Python. Whether it's crafting elegant algorithms or building innovative software solutions, I love the creative process of turning lines of code into functional applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Development Intern Bharat Intern Oct 2023 - Nov 2023

This internship offers me the opportunity to apply my existing Knowledge and Skills and simultaneously acquire new abilities, that will contribute to my personal growth and development.

Worked on projects with the use of Html, CSS & JS, Incredible experience learned lots of new things during making projects like -

- Content Management System
- · Project Management Tool

Data Science Intern

Oasis Infobyte Nov 2023 - Dec 2023

This internship provides me with the chance to put my current knowledge and skills to use while also learning new ones.

Worked on projects with the use of Python, Incredible experience learned lots of new things during making projects like -

- Iris Flower classification
- Unemployment Analysis with Python
- Car Price Prediction with Machine Learning
- Email Spam Detection With Machine Learning
- Sales Prediction Using Python

Web Development Intern

Codsoft Nov 2023 - Dec 2023

I'm able to gain new skills and apply my existing knowledge and abilities thanks to this internship.

Worked on projects with the use of HTML & CSS, Incredible experience learned lots of new things during making projects like -

- Landing Page using HTML & CSS
- Personal Portfolio using HTML & CSS
- · Basic Calculator using CSS, HTML, and JavaScript

MANAS DUTTA

WEB DEVELOPER



CONTACT

+91-9382867219

manasdutta1509@gmail.com

https://manasdutta.my.canva.site/

Garhbeta, West Bengal, India, 721127

EXPERTISE

- C Programming Language
- · Python Programming Language
- HTML
- CSS
- MS Powerpoint
- MS Excel
- GitHub
- Figma

HOBBIES

- · learning from experts
- · exploring video games
- · singing in the mind
- · drawing the future
- · excited for futuristic things

PERSONAL DETAILS

Address Vill+Post+PS - Garhbeta

Dist - Paschim Medinipur State - West Bengal India 721127

Date of Birth 15 / 09 / 2004

Gender Male

Nationality Indian

Marital Status Single

PROJECTS

NETFLIX clone using HTML, CSS & JAVASCRIPT

I've successfully built a functional Netflix clone using HTML & CSS. This project allowed me to delve into the intricacies of front-end development and gain a deeper understanding of web technologies.

Restaurant Website using HTML, CSS & JAVASCRIPT

I've successfully built a functional Restaurant Website using HTML & CSS. I was able to learn more about web technologies and the complexities of front-end development through this project.

Landing Page using HTML, CSS & JAVASCRIPT

I've successfully built a functional Developer Landing Page using HTML & CSS. I've been eager to learn about additional web technologies and the complicated nature of front-end programming throughout this project.

Tribute Page using HTML, CSS & JAVASCRIPT

I've successfully built a functional A. P. J. Abdul Kalam Tribute Page using HTML & CSS. Through this project, I was able to learn more about web technologies and dig into the complicated world of front-end programming.

Restaurant Billing using C

Just unveiled the Restaurant Billing Code I developed in C programming. It's all about enhancing the dining experience through innovation

Rock Paper Scissors game using C

I coded my own Rock-Paper-Scissors game in C! Sharpening my programming skills one game at a time.

WhatsApp clone using Figma

I redesigned WhatsApp for ios with the help of Figma software. It has some improvement from the WhatsApp main ios vesion. It helps to improve the UI/UX of WhatsApp.

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the above information is true to best of my knowledge.

Manas Dutta

Manas Dutta